<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Suppernatural fan app</string>
    <string name="action_settings">share</string>
    <string name="season1_desc">suppernatural season 1 starts with flashback ,22years ago showing sam winchester as an infant, his mother is killed by some suppernatural force,sams father \"john winchester\" and his brother \"dean winchester\" who is roughly 5 year old saves sam but are not able to save sam\'s and deans mother \"mary winchester\",after seeing his wife killed by something like that john decided to findout what happened to her,he comes to know that something suppernatural is responsible for mary\'s death so john becomes obsessed with killing the thing which killed his wife , he becomes hunter he learns about different monsters and ways to kill them he also trains his very young sons to become hunters,both sam and dean beccomes very good hunters but when sam says he wants to go to college john refuses and says he should be there hunting so sam rebels,john says if he leaves he should never come back.sam leaves to have a normal life which he always wanted,he goes to stanford university and gets full scollarship he also finds a girlfriend named jessica but after two years one night dean appears on Sam\'s doorstep bearing the news that their father has gone missing while on a hunting trip and needs his help to find him after some aurguing Sam agrees to help him in the search.\n</string>
    <string name="season1_desc2">The brothers trace John and find\'s more clues about their father\'s possible location and help solve the ghost murder mystery their father had been working on before he disappeared. After all was said and done however and John was yet to be found, Sam declines his brother\'s invitation to continue the search and conduct more hunts, opting instead to return to his life with Jessica. Unfortunately, shortly after arriving back in his apartment, he finds her pinned to the bedroom ceiling, bleeding from the abdomen. As Sam watches helplessly she bursts into flames and dies in the same manner as his mother, twenty-two years to the day afterwards. Dean rescues his brother from the burning apartment, and the bereaved Sam decides to join Dean in the search for their father who may have answers about the demon who killed his mother and his girlfriend. the Winchester brothers pick up their fathers trail, traveling the back roads and small towns..Eventually the brothers locate their father, and he reveals the extent of his knowledge of the demon that killed Mary, and his intention to kill it. At first he opposes the boys\' involvement because he fears losing them, but eventually he yields. Together, the Winchesters search for a special weapon: the Colt, which was created during the Battle of the Alamo and at the time of Halley\'s Comet passing. Being made by the legendary Samuel Colt, for a hunter, the gun has the ability to destroy any creature, with a well placed shot. All three Winchesters, after recovering the Colt from a band of vampires, band together and start to hunt the demon in earnest. However, due to a series of catastrophic events , they are eventually overpowered by the demon. While possessing John the demon nearly tortures Dean to death before Sam is able to and shoot it in the leg with the Colt. Sam tries to rush Dean and John to the hospital, but a demon then possesses a semi truck driver and plows into Dean\'s Impala. Demolishing it and leaving all three Winchesters incapacitated inside the wreckage.</string>
    <string name="season2_desc">At the beginning of season two, the trio are rescued via MEDEVAC and taken to the hospital, but due to his extended injures caused by both the demon\'s torture and the car accident, Dean is comatose. John summons the demon to make a deal and trades the gun and his own life for Dean\'s.\n</string>
    <string name="season2_desc2">Both Dean and Sam struggle to cope with John\'s death while trying to continue their job. As they continue to hunt any supernatural spirit they find, they come across many people that share the same story as Sam, a mother who mysteriously dies in their nurseries when the children were 6 months old. These \"special children\" each discovered recently that they have some sort of psychic power. In the light of these revelations, Dean reveals to Sam that their father (just before giving his life to the demon) had told Dean he had to save Sam or be forced to kill him. Various revelations occur throughout the rest of the season that lead the pair to believe these psychics are being trained to participate in an army that the demon will lead in a coming apocalypse.\n</string>
    <string name="season2_desc3">After several months of \"by-the-book\" jobs, Sam disappears while ordering food at a diner. He awakens in a ghost town with four other psychics, two of whom he had met in prior episodes (Ava from Hunted and Andy from Simon Said). There, in a dream, the demon reveals to Sam he has brought all of them to the town to compete against one another and the winner (the only one left alive) would become the leader of the demon\'s army. The two innocent psychics are killed, before Ava (who has killed Andy by summoning a murderous demon) is revealed to be a demonic familiar herself. Jake, an Army soldier who claims he was abducted from Afghanistan, kills Ava by snapping her neck after taking her by surprise. Dean has been frantically trying to locate his brother, discovering the Roadhouse has been burned to the ground, leaving Ash dead and Ellen missing. With the help of Andy, who can \"beam information\" directly into people\'s brains, Bobby discerns where Sam and the others are (a haunted ghost town in rural, fictional \"Cold Oak, South Dakota\"). Upon their arrival, Dean and Bobby watch in horror as Sam is stabbed in the back by the only other survivor, Jake. Sam dies in Dean\'s arms.\n</string>
    <string name="season2_desc4">In the season finale, Dean, distraught and unable to cope with the loss of his brother, believes that he has let Sam down. His mind made up, Dean sets off without Bobby, leaving Sam\'s body behind. He makes a deal with the demon at the crossroads, his soul for Sam\'s. The demon agrees and brings Sam back from the dead. However, she tells Dean that she will only give him one more year to live, and if he tries in any way to prevent his death, Sam will drop dead on the spot. When Dean returns, he finds his brother alive and well and unaware of all that has happened. After everything Dean went through knowing that his father had died for him, he wants to protect Sam and decides not to tell his brother that Jake had killed him.\n</string>
    <string name="season2_desc5">Ellen, who was away when the roadhouse burned down, finds Bobby, Dean, and Sam and shows them a map that Ash had prepared just before his death. They discover that an elaborate gate was constructed by Samuel Colt to bar an entrance from hell. The demon tells Jake that he must open the gate and that the Colt is the key. The whole group arrives to stop Jake, who is beyond surprised to see Sam and insists that he killed him. Jake gets the gate open but is shot to death by Sam. \n</string>
    <string name="season2_desc6">The demon returns and taunts Dean with the possibility that the Sam that Dean has had resurrected, may not be \"one hundred percent pure Sam.\" He then attempts to kill Dean. However, John Winchester, who has escaped from hell, manages to save his son. Dean shoots and kills the demon with the last remaining bullet in the Colt, and John\'s soul departs, no longer condemned to hell. Bobby and Ellen are able to close the gate, but not before hundreds of souls and demons escape. Sam is suspicious and wants to know why Jake insisted that he had killed him. Dean is then forced to reveal the deal he had made at the crossroads, and Sam, who is upset over the sacrifice Dean has made, promises to save him.</string>
    <string name="season3_desc">The first episode of season 3, \"The Magnificent Seven\", introduces one new character – a young blonde woman named \"Ruby\" (played by Katie Cassidy) who uses a demon-killing dagger.\n</string>
    <string name="season3_desc2">Ruby is a demon that shows particular interest in Sam. At her urgings, Sam discovers that all of his mother\'s friends and contacts have been steadily killed off over the years by the yellow-eyed demon. Ruby won\'t discuss what it is she wants, but says that not all demons are the same or have the same motivations. She also says if Sam helps her she can save Dean. In the episode Sin City she describes herself as a \"little fallen angel\" on Sam\'s shoulder. She also assisted Bobby in successfully rebuilding and restoring power to the Colt. At the end of \"Malleus Maleficarum\" Ruby tells Dean that most demons were once human - but they forget what it\'s like to be human. For some reason she remembers, which is at least one of the reasons that she helps the brothers. Dean and Sam also discover that when Ruby was human, she sold her soul to a demon.In \"Bad Day at Black Rock\", it is discovered that John had a secret storage room in Black Rock. Dean and Sam find that an object from the room is missing and set out to find it. The boys track down the burglars and discover that the missing object is a rabbit\'s foot. This rabbit\'s foot brings the boys to a series of lucky events until it is stolen by Bela (played by Lauren Cohan), a thief and merchant out to use the supernatural world as a paycheck - and Sam\'s luck turns really bad.Described by Bobby Singer as \"pretty damn far from a Hunter\", Bela is an attractive Englishwoman who acquires magical objects for wealthy clients. Bela is amoral, claiming that she will sell anything to anyone for the right price. She only shows an ability to help Sam and Dean when it benefits her. Dean threatens to kill Bela numerous times, since she continuously tricks and pranks the brothers. It was implied that she once killed one of her own family members.Sam seems to have developed a sense of no remorse for killing demons since his return to life at the end of Season 2. This includes Jake, Father Gil/Casey, and the crossroads demon. There are multiple discussions throughout the season involving Dean realizing these changes, and confirming them with Bobby, who does believe the yellow eyed demon (who\'s real name was revealed as Azazel) was telling the truth that what Dean brought back may not be \"100% pure Sam\".In the episode \"Bedtime Stories\", Sam and Dean argue over whether using the newly rebuilt Colt will help give them the upper hand in breaking Dean\'s deal with the crossroads demon who revived Sam. At the end of the episode, Sam takes the Colt and, while Dean is asleep, visits the demon and threatens her. She tells Sam, however, that killing her will not break the deal since her boss holds the contract. Sam shoots and kills the demon anyway, along with the woman it was possessing.In the episode \"Dream a Little Dream of Me\" Bela is able to steal the colt from Sam and Dean. The following episode \"Mystery Spot\" brought back the Trickster who told Sam he has to stop trying to save Dean from dying.Sam\'s replacement chosen to apparently lead the army of demons was revealed to be named Lilith, a white -eyed demon who has possessed a little girl, first appearing in the episode \"Jus in Bello\".</string>
    <string name="season4_desc">After spending four long, horrific months in Hell, Dean Winchester is miraculously raised from the Underworld and resurrected by an angel of the Lord God Himself named Castiel, one of several angels who appears throughout the season. After Dean reunites with his father-figure friend Bobby and his brother Sam, the rest of the season follows the brothers, with the help of their friend Bobby, as they work with Castiel and his subordinate and friend Uriel, a fellow angel, to stop Lilith\'s plan of breaking the 66 Seals to unlock a cage in Hell, which will allow the release of the fallen archangel Lucifer himself, AKA Satan or The Devil, who was once the favored angel of God but rebelled against Heaven for refusing to serve humans and therefore was cast down and banished.Along the way, the boys meet a girl named Anna who not only has the ability to hear angels but is also a fallen angel herself. Eventually, angels turn up dead and the angels capture Alastair, Hell\'s Grand Torturer demon who seems to know Dean well, and they ask Dean to torture him with them assuming its the demons killing the angels, but Alastair, before he dies, says its not the demons. And eventually, Castiel learns that his own brother Uriel turns out to not only be working for Lucifer, but has convinced several loyalist angels to join him and to free Lucifer from his cage. Along the way, Dean learns that he broke the first seal while he was in Hell by being convinced by Alastair to slaughter innocent souls in the Underworld, especially when he reveals to Sam that he wasn\'t in Hell for four months but instead 40 years. Additionally, the brothers meet a Prophet of the Lord named Chuck.Sam and Dean\'s relationship is also strained as Sam starts siding with Ruby over Dean. He also begins to give into his demonic side by drinking demon blood to become strong enough to kill Lilith. After tracking down and killing Lilith, Sam learns her death is actually the final seal and Ruby was deceiving him all along. Dean arrives too late to stop him, but the brothers kill Ruby as Lucifer\'s cage opens up beneath them and he released upon the world</string>
    <string name="season5_desc">After spending four long, horrific months in Hell, Dean Winchester is miraculously raised from the Underworld and resurrected by an angel of the Lord God Himself named Castiel, one of several angels who appears throughout the season. After Dean reunites with his father-figure friend Bobby and his brother Sam, the rest of the season follows the brothers, with the help of their friend Bobby, as they work with Castiel and his subordinate and friend Uriel, a fellow angel, to stop Lilith\'s plan of breaking the 66 Seals to unlock a cage in Hell, which will allow the release of the fallen archangel Lucifer himself, AKA Satan or The Devil, who was once the favored angel of God but rebelled against Heaven for refusing to serve humans and therefore was cast down and banished.Along the way, the boys meet a girl named Anna who not only has the ability to hear angels but is also a fallen angel herself. Eventually, angels turn up dead and the angels capture Alastair, Hell\'s Grand Torturer demon who seems to know Dean well, and they ask Dean to torture him with them assuming its the demons killing the angels, but Alastair, before he dies, says its not the demons. And eventually, Castiel learns that his own brother Uriel turns out to not only be working for Lucifer, but has convinced several loyalist angels to join him and to free Lucifer from his cage. Along the way, Dean learns that he broke the first seal while he was in Hell by being convinced by Alastair to slaughter innocent souls in the Underworld, especially when he reveals to Sam that he wasn\'t in Hell for four months but instead 40 years. Additionally, the brothers meet a Prophet of the Lord named Chuck.Sam and Dean\'s relationship is also strained as Sam starts siding with Ruby over Dean. He also begins to give into his demonic side by drinking demon blood to become strong enough to kill Lilith. After tracking down and killing Lilith, Sam learns her death is actually the final seal and Ruby was deceiving him all along. Dean arrives too late to stop him, but the brothers kill Ruby as Lucifer\'s cage opens up beneath them and he released upon the world</string>
    <string name="season6_desc">The sixth season begins about a year after the end happenings of the fifth with Dean living a normal life with Lisa Braeden and her son Ben. Sam mysteriously and miraculously returns to Earth and reunites with Dean, who leaves his new life behind. Sam has been working with their grandfather, Samuel Campbell (their mother\'s father), in order to capture the Alpha monsters (first of the gene pool). Bobby eventually gets his soul back from the crossroads demon Crowley, who has apparently become the King of Hell. It is eventually discovered that Samuel is following Crowley\'s orders in exchange for the resurrection of his daughter, Sam and Dean\'s mother. Castiel is barely helpful anymore because a civil war in Heaven against the archangel Raphael (who wants to take over Heaven, free both Michael and Lucifer from the Cage, and start the Apocalypse again) has taken its toll. Crowley wants to use the Alpha Monsters to locate Purgatory, a supernatural realm that is filled with the souls of every monster that has ever been killed (vampires, werewolves, wendigos, skinwalkers, even shapeshifters etc.) and in which there are a vast collection of souls that could be used for power. Castiel brought back Sam without his soul, and Dean implores the help of the Horseman Death in order to retrieve it. Death puts a wall up in Sam\'s mind so that he will not remember Hell. Sam\'s original personality is restored with no memory of the past year and a half. It turns out Castiel made a deal with Crowley for both of them to receive half of the souls in Purgatory. Dean doesn\'t like the idea and tries to stop the duo. To stop the Winchesters and Bobby Singer, Castiel knocks down the mental barrier in Sam. Castiel betrays Crowley, who then allies himself with Raphael and performs the ritual to open the doors of Purgatory. It fails because they had fake dog\'s blood and Castiel appears full of power from having done the ritual himself. He obliterates Raphael and Crowley escapes. When the Winchesters try to reason with Castiel, he reveals that he is not an angel anymore, he has become the new God.</string>
    <string name="season7_desc">"In season seven, the events take place right after the angel Castiel absorbed the souls of Purgatory declares himself as the new God. And the \"mutated angel\" goes around the planet to try and finish his \"work\". But eventually, thanks to a little bit of help from the Horseman Death, the Winchesters convince the angel to return all the souls back to Purgatory. But Castiel manages to return all but the souls of some older creatures. Something in which the Winchesters will find themselves in an increasingly sinister, changing landscape, as they go up against this new foe, which is unlike anything they've ever fought before: the Leviathans, the very first beasts created by God, but were then locked away in Purgatory for being too destructive. The brothers will find their old tricks, weapons and hiding places all rendered useless. All they'll have is each other. And the certainty that, like the last of the cowboy outlaws, whatever they face, they're not going down without a fight.Season seven finds Dean and Sam reeling from the loss of Bobby and without the help of Castiel. Sam's violent memories of Hell threaten to overtake him, threatening not just his life, but his brother's as well. Meanwhile, Dean struggles under the weight of a secret that threatens to tear them apart. And even as the brothers traverse the backroads of America, hunting things that go bump in the night, something is coming for them. They are about to face an enemy more cunning and adaptable than any they've ever fought. As the landscape around them becomes increasingly treacherous, the tools they've come to rely upon will be stripped away. Our heroes, like so many outlaws before them, will find themselves utterly outmatched and outgunned and pushed to their limites, with no one to rely on but each other.As the season progresses the Leviathans become a much greater threat where Sam and Dean are forced to form an alliance with a resurrected Castiel, Meg, Crowley, a ghostly Bobby Singer and the prophet Kevin Tran to defeat the Leviathans and their leader Dick Roman with a weapon designed by God. Bobby begins to turn into a vengeful spirit forcing Sam and Dean to destroy him. Dean manages to kill Dick but the after effects cause him and Castiel to end up in Purgatory while Crowley abducts Meg and Kevin and with Bobby dead Sam is completely alone... "</string>
    <string name="season8_desc">One year after the defeat of the Leviathans, Dean escapes Purgatory, with a vampire-comrade-in-arms named Benny, and reunites with Sam who has retired from hunting much to Dean\'s anger. Not long after Dean discovers that Kevin had escaped Crowley\'s abduction months ago which Sam was unaware of. Kevin reveals that he stole another Word of God from Crowley about Demons and discovered the means of closing Hell forever with all demons inside. Now reunited Sam and Dean embark on their monster hunts while Kevin continues to translate the tablet to stop Crowley and his plotting. \n</string>
    <string name="season8_desc1">Sam and Dean\'s relationship is challenged as Sam stopped hunting for a year which he claims is because he had no one to force him anymore with Dean and Castiel gone, Bobby dead and Kevin and Meg missing. Dean, however, remains in contact with Benny, who is trying to live without killing but is missing Purgatory but Sam becomes angry that Dean would let a vampire live. \n</string>
    <string name="season8_desc2">The season also features flashbacks in both Sam and Dean\'s past year on Earth and Purgatory. For Dean he constantly fought monsters everyday for a year in Purgatory until Benny saved him and told him of a portal which could transport humans out. Dean and Benny find Castiel and the three fight past Leviathans to make it to the portal but Castiel refuses to leave. As for Sam, he retired from hunting and met a woman named Amelia and lived a normal life with her. However, once she discovers that her husband, a soldier presumed KIA, was still alive, Sam left to allow her to reunite with him. Eventually Castiel returns, freed from Purgatory by the mysterious but powerful angel Naomi, who has apparently taken control of Heaven and puts Castiel under her control to spy on the Winchesters for her own motives. Meanwhile, Amelia returns to Sam to re-connect but Sam pushes her away for good while Benny helps Dean by dying and returning to Purgatory to help Sam and Bobby pass through Purgatory to Earth and subsequently chooses to stay there. \n</string>
    <string name="season8_desc3">Kevin eventually learns the three trials for sealing Hell from the Demon Tablet: kill a Hellhound and bathe in its blood, free a soul from Hell (who turns out to be Bobby) wrongfully imprisoned, and finally cure a demon who they choose to use on Crowley. However, the Winchesters and Castiel learn from Meg, before she is killed by Crowley, of the Angel Tablet which Naomi tries to have Castiel steal for her own uses but he resists and flees from everyone. Additionally, Sam and Dean encounter their grandfather Henry and a powerful demon named Abaddon who is a Knight of Hell, among the oldest and most powerful demons. While Henry is killed and Abaddon is decommissioned, the brothers lean of a bunker belonging to the Men of Letters, the collectors of information on the supernatural who entrust a few hunters to handle the most powerful monsters. In the midst of the trials, Sam and Dean encounter an angel named Metatron, the Scribe of God and the creator of the tablets who then reveals the nature of the angel tablet to Castiel: to seal Heaven and its angels and works with Castiel to fulfill this mission. Meanwhile, after Crowley begins killing Sam and Dean\'s old friends, they decide to give in.\n</string>
    <string name="season8_desc4">In the season finale, Sam and Dean manage to capture Crowley to use him as the last trial and cure him while Naomi continues looking for Castiel and captures Metatron, forcing Castiel to work with Dean to finish the angel trials. Meanwhile, Sam is interrupted by Abaddon but fends her off as Crowley begins to show signs of humanity. Naomi realizes that Metatron is not planning to seal Heaven but is planning to break Heaven and cause the angels to fall and that if Sam completes the final trial, he will die as God wanted. Dean returns to Sam and in an emotional breakdown they make up for their years of mistakes but Sam passes out while Metatron betrays Castiel and takes his grace, turning him human. Moments later the angels of Heaven fall all across the Earth as Sam, Dean, Kevin, Castiel, and Crowley are forced to watch helplessly.</string>
    <string name="season9_desc">Immediately after the fall of the angels caused by the angel Metatron, the Scribe of God, Sam falls into a coma from the effects of the trials to close the gates of Hell and almost dies. With Castiel unable to help (having lost his grace), Dean seeks the aid of another angel named Ezekiel, whose only option to save Sam from his wounds is to possess him. Dean accepts, and helps Ezekiel trick Sam into giving his consent against his knowledge. The three of them, with Kevin (and Crowley as their prisoner), work to find a means to put the angels back in Heaven and are also forced to deal with Knight of Hell, Abaddon, who is attempting to seize control of Hell in Crowley\'s absence and enforce her reign of Hell on earth. Also a newly human Castiel must continue to run from the thousands of angels who blame him for their setbacks including many of whom are now lead by Bartholomew and Malachi seeking to restore themselves back to Heaven under their respective leadership\'s. Sam and Dean (with the help of Ezekiel) deal with regular hunting cases with help from old friends such as Charlie and Jody, but over time Sam begins to notice that something isn\'t right with him which Dean wants to tell Sam about but Ezekiel insists that his presence must remain secret. Eventually, Metatron returns to Earth and Ezekiel is revealed to actually be the angel Gadreel, the former protector of the Garden of Eden picked by God to protect the Garden but failed by letting Lucifer into the Garden and was then punished by being locked away in Heaven\'s darkest dungeon. Metatron makes a deal with Gadreel to rebuild Heaven together by allowing certain angels to return which Gadreel, seeking to redeem himself accepts. Dean discovers Gadreel\'s deception and tries to warn Sam, but Gadreel takes full control and kills Kevin. Meanwhile, Castiel reclaims his powers by stealing the grace of another angel. Dean and Castiel team up with Crowley to expel Gadreel from Sam\'s body, but are forced to let the King of Hell go in exchange for his help. \n</string>
    <string name="season9_desc1">Sam is furious at Dean\'s deception, and their relationship becomes strained as they struggle to deal with Kevin\'s death. While Sam is still at the Bunker and Castiel starts a mission to find Metatron on his own and stay clear of Bartholomew, who eventually finds him and tries to convince Castiel to join him, Dean then teams up with Crowley in his hunt for Abaddon to find the only weapons that can kill a Knight of Hell, the First Blade and the Mark of Cain. Both of which Dean acquires from Cain himself, the first born son of Adam and Eve, who killed his brother Abel and became the original Knight of Hell as well as the trainer and creator of the rest of the Knights, including Abaddon. Sam helps Castiel look for Gadreel, while Castiel comes face to face with Bartholomew who wants him to join his faction of followers hunting for Metatron. Castiel disagrees with Bartholomew\'s ruthless methods and kills him in self-defense, causing a number of angels to ask Castiel to lead them (much to his chagrin). Dean eventually finds Abaddon and kills her, but the Mark of Cain begins to affect him, bestowing him with great strength, but also a painful desire to kill. Meanwhile, Metatron continues to play God with the power of the angel tablet and starts enacting public miracles to become a deity to mankind and they begin to slaughter and praise in Metatron\'s name. Gadreel grows tired of Metatron\'s lies and defects, teaming up with Castiel to try and stop him.\n</string>
    <string name="season9_desc2">In the season finale, Sam and Castiel worry about the Mark\'s influence on Dean, but eventually realize that he\'s their best shot at defeating Metatron. Castiel and Gadreel try to infiltrate Heaven to destroy the angel tablet and cut off Metatron\'s power, allowing Dean to kill the angel, but they are caught and put in Heaven\'s dungeon. Gadreel is forced to sacrifice himself as part of a spell to free Castiel. Meanwhile, Sam arrives too late to stop Metatron from stabbing Dean through the heart and his brother dies in his arms. Castiel manages to trick Metatron and take back Heaven, but chooses to spare his life and locks him in Heaven\'s dungeon though is dying from his draining grace. Sam tries to summon Crowley to fix Dean, but instead Crowley shows up in the bunker of his own choice where Dean\'s body has been placed and puts the First Blade back into his hands, which revives Dean as a demon.</string>
    <string name="season10_desc">Season 10 begins with Sam\'s frantic search for his missing brother, who is gone without a trace. The road to recovering the wayward Dean takes Sam down dark paths, with consequences that will shake the boys to their core. Along the way, Sam encounters a former US marine named Cole Trenton, who apparently knows Dean and wants revenge for Dean killing his father. Meanwhile, Castiel, with the aid of Hannah, has to pick up the pieces in the aftermath of Metatron\'s campaign. But with his grace failing and rogue angels still on the loose, Cas faces the ticking clock of his own mortality. After Sam learns that Dean is a demon, because of Crowley and the Mark of Cain, Sam eventually finds him, with help from Crowley, but so does Cole. While Dean and Cole meet and duke it out, Dean overpowers Cole and nearly kills him. But Sam manages to trap Dean with holy water and handcuffs carved with devils-trap symbols.\n</string>
    <string name="season10_desc1">After giving Crowley the First Blade, Sam takes Dean back to the Men of Letters bunker to cure him. Castiel and Hannah are on the way to help but are delayed because of a rogue angel who injures Cas and tortures Hannah until Crowley shows and takes the grace of the angel and gives it to Cas. As Sam continues to cure Dean, he eventually escapes the devil\'s trap and tries to kill Sam but Castiel arrives, overpowers Dean and they continue curing him until he is finally human. As the season progresses, all-new threats emerge to once again push all of our heroes to their limits.\n</string>
    <string name="season10_desc2">One such threat is the appearance of a very powerful witch named Rowena, who also turns out to be Crowley\'s mother and has the power to kill demons. He captures her, but she convinces him to let her live in Hell so they can reunite and be a family again. Meanwhile, while Castiel and Hannah still take care of the rogue angels, Sam and Dean work normal, everyday cases: dealing with not just demons but also ghosts, monsters (vampires, werewolves, and shapeshifters), deities, and again with angels. They also help out their friend sheriff Jody Mills. However, Dean is suffering from the effects of the Mark and Sam and Castiel desperately try to help him and find a cure, or at the very least, a way to get rid of it, even going as far as to torture Metatron.\n</string>
    <string name="season10_desc3">Eventually, the Winchesters\' friend Charlie returns from Oz as well and after combining her with her alter-ego, which she created from the Wizard of Oz to win the war in Oz, she agrees to help the boys find a cure for the Mark, but Dean is starting to give up and live with it. Hannah eventually abandons her mission with Cas and returns to Heaven. Later on, another one of those threats is the original bearer of the Mark, Cain himself, who has fallen under its influence as well and has started killing his descendants to rid the world of his tainted bloodline, which was stained the moment he killed his brother, Abel. After trapping him in a Devil\'s trap, Dean and Cain square off in a barn and Dean defeats him, stabbing him with the First Blade, while Sam, Castiel, and Crowley wait for him.\n</string>
    <string name="season10_desc4">Dean has given up on finding a cure, but Sam still continues to search, going behind Dean\'s back and convincing Castiel to come see a psychic to contact the boy\'s surrogate father, Bobby, in Heaven, in order to get Metatron on Earth. After Sam and Castiel remove Metatron\'s grace, he reveals that he doesn\'t know how to remove the Mark, but he mentions that Castiel\'s grace still remains and takes him to it. However, Metatron finds and takes the Demon tablet but not before Cas manages to get his grace back and returns to his status as a Seraph. Sometime after, Charlie contacts the brothers about a possible way to remove the Mark with a book called the Book of the Damned, a very powerful dark magic book that was in possession of the Styne Family, an ancient family that was the inspiration for Mary Shelley\'s Frankenstein and has consisted entirely of magic practitioners mixed with vastly superior surgical skills for multiple generations.\n</string>
    <string name="season10_desc5">Sam calls upon Rowena, Castiel, Charlie, and Crowley to read the book and find a way to remove the Mark. However, one of the Styne members kills Charlie and Dean becomes hell-bent on revenge, giving in to the Mark. After the Styne family captures Dean, Dean falls under the Mark\'s influence, kills the entire Styne family, savagely beats and almost kills Castiel when he tried to stop Dean, and disappears. He heads to a Mexican restaurant and summons Death, the Pale Horseman himself, to kill him. However Death reveals that the Mark not only makes Dean unkillable, thus even he can\'t kill Dean, he also tells Dean that if he even removes the Mark without passing it along to another host, it will unleash the Darkness, a powerful and destructive primordial force that predates the Earth, the Universe, the Archangels, and even God. He also tells Dean that after God and the Archangels fought the Darkness in a horrifying war, God created the Mark of Cain to lock away the Darkness, and sealed it away using the Mark, which was originally borne by Lucifer himself. The Mark revealed itself as a curse after corrupting Lucifer as he became jealous of humans, who was banished to Hell for his crimes against humans and God. Lucifer passed the Mark on to Cain before his imprisonment in his Cage, who then transferred it to Dean.\n</string>
    <string name="season10_desc6">Death tells Dean that he can send Dean somewhere else so that the Darkness remains sealed and the Mark remains intact on a host, but he has to kill Sam. After Sam and Dean fight, Dean is ready to kill Sam with Death\'s Scythe, but ironically, Dean kills Death at the last second due to his love for his brother. After that, the Mark is removed from Dean\'s arm, thanks to the spell from the Book of the Damned cast by Rowena, who later pins Castiel and Crowley and puts Castiel under her attack dog spell so he will kill Crowley. Elsewhere, the Darkness is released.\n</string>
    <string name="season11_desc">Following the release of the Darkness, the season follows the Winchesters and their allies as they find themselves fighting the most powerful supernatural entity they\'ve ever faced, unlike anything else they\'ve ever gone up against before.Immediately after its release, and blowing over the Impala, Sam sees that Dean is gone and goes to look for him, finding him in a field where Dean had a conversation with the Darkness, which apparently turns out to be, or at least, takes the form of a woman in a black dress. Dean says that she thanked him for setting her free.Meanwhile, Castiel is still suffering from the dog attack spell the witch Rowena put him under and starts to attack others. He also remembers that when he attacked Crowley, the King of Hell escaped from his current vessel and into another one. He then hires the demons to get rid of the spell holding his vessel in place.As Sam and Dean drive, they find a Sheriff\'s deputy named Jenna Nickerson and head to a hospital to help others. Upon arriving there, they find people with black veins called Rabids, people who have their inner darkness out.This being an effect of the release of the Darkness. They also find a human baby in the mix named Amara. Meanwhile, as a manhunt for him begins, Castiel prays to the angels, begging them to help him from hurting others and is willing to take whatever punishment they bring him.\n</string>
    <string name="season11_desc1">As Dean, Jenna, and the baby make it out, Sam gets infected and starts to sprout black veins. Eventually, after he prays to God for help, he encounters a Reaper named Billie who is apparently disappointed that Death is dead and says that the next time Sam and Dean are killed, she will ensure that they stay dead and even that she will toss them into the Empty, a place no soul nor entity nor being can escape from. As the angels find Cas, they start to torture him and after Hannah arrives, she explains that alarms are going off in Heaven. He implies that those alarms are for the release of the Darkness. As the tortures continue, Castiel escapes and Hannah dies trying to save him. Crowley manages to get back in his vessel and his subordinates reveal that the Darkness is free, especially that when Michael and Lucifer themselves apparently shouted throughout Hell from the Cage.Dean and Jenna go to her grandmothers house and while they realize Amara is levitating objects, she called Dean and her grandmother called an exorcist, who turns out to be Crowley impersonating a priest. However, back at the hospital, Sam finds a cure for the rabids: Holy Fire. And he makes a ring of holy fire and cures a few others as well. The baby turns out to be Amara as a child as Dean finds the Mark of Cain on her. Amara also sucks out Jenna\'s soul and she becomes soulless, like how Sam once was. After Crowley kills her, Dean attacks him as he plans to take the baby, but fails as the baby walks out and quickly grows up. Sam and Dean eventually reunite and find Cas at the bunker while Crowley finds Amara and takes her to Hell of humans as an offering.\n</string>
    <string name="season11_desc2">The Winchesters look for ways to find and stop the Darkness, but first they search for Rowena to undo the spell on Cas. They find her and she does so, but she escapes. And in Hell, as Crowley becomes Amara\'s \"uncle\", she starts to become hungry and sucks the black cloud of demons, literately eating them. Eventually, Sam reveals to Dean that he has been having visions about an being he describes as the opposite of the Darkness, which he thinks is God himself.And while Sam and Dean work on ordinary cases involving ghosts, monsters, and even along the way Imagionary Friends, the brothers and Cas also start searching for ways to defeat the Darkness. Even after finding her where Crowley\'s keeping her, Dean doesn\'t appear to strike at her and he fails and she escapes. Meanwhile, at the place, Sam\'s visions start to become more revealing, she he starts to have visions of Lucifer\'s Cage. Castiel eventually finds Metatron, who has started a business of catching what he calls reality but is also miserable about his current status. After beating and throwing him, Castiel askes Metatron what he knows about the Darkness, considering he was God\'s scribe. Metatron reveals that in order to created the Earth, Heaven, even the entire Universe, in order to start creation itself for that matter, God didn\'t only imprison the Darkness, but he had to betray and sacrifice her and Metatron says that the Darkness is the only thing God\'s really ever known, his only kin...his older sister.\n</string>
    <string name="season11_desc3">Although Dean hates the idea, they intend to go the Limbo, the deepest place in Hell, and speak to Lucifer about the Darkness. They enlist the help of Rowena to summon him. And when Dean goes to find Amara at a church where she attacks people, Sam awaits outside of a supernatural cage in Limbo surrounded by powerful fire and covered in enochian sigils, and eventually, Lucifer himself appears in the cage, manifested as his original vessel, Nick. He and Sam talk about the Darkness and how to stop her while Amara and Dean talk about her issue with her brother. After three angels find her and try to attack her, she kills them all and summon a powerful smiting attack that knocks her out. In Hell, Lucifer says that he will help them stop her, but only if he possesses Sam and returns to Earth. Sam says no and Lucifer extinguishes the fire, erases the warding, and summons Sam in the cage and still tries to make him say yes, especially when he reveals that it wasn\'t God who sent Sam the visions, but it was Lucifer. When the Darkness was set free, it damaged the cage and allowed Lucifer to reach out to Sam. Though Sam strongly considers, he still says no and Lucifer starts to attack him.Rowena reveals that Lucifer came to her in a dream and said he needed her help to get Sam to him and she would join him. But, after Cas finds Amara, having survived the attack, she summons him to Dean with a messages and eventually, as Rowena conjures the spell to banish Lucifer, Dean and Cas head down to the cage and help Sam survive in a fight against Lucifer. As Lucifer also kills Cas, Lucifer is banished by Rowena. After leaving Hell, Cas apparently stays and reveals the before Lucifer could be banished back to the Cage, Cas said yes to him and Lucifer possessed him. After freeing and then killing Rowena, Lucifer takes back Hell and makes Crowley his slave, calling him \"Puppy\".\n</string>
    <string name="season11_desc4">Meanwhile, Sam and Dean eventually find possible ways to defeat Amara, using Hands of God, powerful objects said to contain the power of God himself. Even after finding one, Sam, Dean, Rowena, and Crowley try to get Lucifer out of Castiel\'s body but it fails and he absorbs the power of the Hand of God and uses it on Amara, but it fails and he is taken against this will by Amara. And she starts to torture him to draw out God. And as fate would have it, eventually, God himself finally returns. After having a conversation with Metatron and reconciling with Lucifer, he decides to help stop her. And though his original plan of weakening her with Witches, Demons, and Angels and trying to imprison her again using the Mark fails, Amara fatally attacks God.Although they think Amara seems impossible to destroy, God tells Sam, Dean, Cas, Crowley and Rowena that she does have one weakness: Light with the power of 10,000 suns. So they collect souls to build a bomb. And Dean is the one to bear it. After talking with Amara, whom starts to feel bad about attacking and nearly killing her brother, Dean convinces her to forgive him. So she summons him to a garden area and the two reconcile and decide to go off together for a while. However, Amara leaves Dean with a thank you gift and he finds his mother alive and resurrected. However the the bunker awaits a British woman who banishes Cas with a banishing sigil and shoots Sam, leaving his fate unknown.</string>

    <string name="leviiathan_desc">leviathan\'s are one of very first creation of god they were created before angels and humans,they are said to be immortal,they bleed black ghuu ,they can be slowed down by cutting their head,borax does damage them,they can shift shape and also download the information from the brain of human they have transformed into,they were very distructive so god himself had to shut them into purgotory</string>
    <string name="angels_desc">angels are warrior\'s of god,they are very strong they fight for heaven,arc angels are strongest of all angels they carry angel blade with them,angel blade is only thing that can kill an angel,angels lost their wings when they fell from heaven because of megatron</string>
    <string name="demons_desc">demons are corrupted souls ,they can possess human body,demons mostly do the cross road deals where they give a persons whatever they want and in exchange they ask for their soul,after 10 years of deal they send hell hounds to kill the person and collect his/her soul,demons can be hurt by holy water and to kill them a special kind of knife is required,an angel blade can also kill them</string>
    <string name="werewolves_desc">like vampires werewolves are created when a human is biten by a werewolf,they look like humans but can transform into wolves,first 4 generations of werewolves can control their transformation and can transform whenever they want but later generations only transforms during full moon,they feed on human heart,they can only be killed by silver knife</string>
    <string name="vampires_desc">when someone is bitten by a vampire he or she transforms into a vampire ,they feed on human blood,they are very strong and the only way to kill them is by choping off their head,dead mans blood works great against them,they mostly hunt in pack,they avoid going in daylight as light hurts their skin</string>
    <string name="spirits_desc">when people die and refuse to go to heaven or hell they stay there as spirits,these spirits are mostly attached to some object,to rest a spirit its remains(mostly bones and flesh but sometimes the objects they are very attached to)should be burned,spiritscan be slowed down by using rock salt or iron</string>
    <string name="sams_desc">Samuel \"Sam\" Winchester (born May 2, 1983) is a hunter as well as a Man of Letters, along with his older brother Dean. He is one of the main protagonists of Supernatural. Both Sam and Dean are related to the Winchester and Campbell families - a Letters family and a Hunting family respectively. The pair also share a bloodline with Cain and Abel. Because of this, Sam was predestined to be the true vessel of the fallen archangel Lucifer (whilst Dean was Michael\'s). Sam is friends with angel Castiel, Prophet Kevin Tran, the demon Meg and former lover turned enemy of demon Ruby. He is also the occasional reluctant ally of demon Crowley and for a time was forced to be an unknowing and unwilling vessel for the angel Gadreel (before expelling him).\n</string>
    <string name="sams_desc1">After the demon Azazel killed their mother, both Sam and Dean were raised in the hunting life by their father John. Sam left the Hunting life to pursue a career in law, and most likely would have married his college sweetheart Jessica Moore. At the series\' start, Sam was reluctant to start hunting again. When Jessica was killed, he was pushed back into the hunting life. However, he has been repeatedly known to try and back out of Hunting in the hope of finally having a normal life as he wanted.\n</string>
    <string name="sams_desc2">Sam is very mentally strong, evidenced by his ability to overpower possession by Lucifer. It has been argued that he is the smarter or more intelligent of the Winchester brothers, although Sam himself would disagree.\n</string>
    <string name="sams_desc3">Over time, Sam has resigned himself to the hunting lifestyle and has repeatedly sacrificed himself for the greater good, highlighting his selfless nature.</string>
    <string name="dean_desc">Dean Winchester (born January 24, 1979) is a human and hunter as well as a member of the Men of Letters with his younger brother Sam. He and his brother are members of the Winchester and Campbell families, and Dean is also the destined vessel of the archangel Michael[1]. He and Sam are also the surrogate sons of Bobby Singer. Dean is best friends with the angel Castiel, close friend to the late prophet Kevin Tran, and reluctant ally of Crowley. Dean has an ex-girlfriend, Lisa Braeden who he lived with for a year when he thought Sam was in Hell. She has a child named Ben, who Dean acted as a father for, and is implied to be the biological father of Ben. Dean is also the former apprentice of Alastair. Both Dean and Sam were raised in the hunting life by their father, after the demon Azazel killed their mother. Dean\'s main role in the series is being the self-appointed guardian of Sam and often going to extreme lengths to protect him regardless of personal cost. Often in these occurrences Dean finds himself the center of a much larger picture. When he was killed by Metatron whilst using the Mark of Cain, Dean returned as a demon and a Knight of Hell loyal only to himself. He was then cured by his brother using purified blood. Eventually, the Mark was removed, but the price was that the Darkness has now been released into the world, something Dean tried to avoid.</string>
    <string name="castiel_desc">Castiel, often shortened to Cas, is a powerful angel of the Lord who was responsible for saving Dean Winchester from Hell,[1] on the archangels\' command. It was his job to help prevent Lilith from breaking the 66 Seals that, once broken, would release Lucifer from his cage[2] in Hell. Once Castiel learned that the angels wished to free Lucifer anyway, he defied his angelic brethren and died trying to help Dean prevent Sam Winchester from breaking the last seal.[3] \n</string>
    <string name="castiel_desc1">After he was killed by Raphael, Castiel was resurrected by God and joined Sam, Dean and Bobby Singer in a quest to stop both Heaven and Hell to prevent the brothers from becoming the vessels of Michael and Lucifer. When the Apocalypse was averted, he was again resurrected with new powers,[4] being promoted to Seraph. He then started a civil war in Heaven to prevent Raphael from restarting the Apocalypse,[5] Thinking he could not be outsmarted by a demon, Castiel teamed up with Crowley to claim the souls of Purgatory.[6] He ended up betraying Crowley and absorbed all the souls, resulting in his powers reaching the level that is much higher than an archangel, but at a high price: the powers that the evil souls granted him had warped Castiel\'s mind, causing him to proclaim himself as the new God.[7]\n</string>
    <string name="castiel_desc2">Castiel later agreed on the advice of Dean to release the souls back into Purgatory. While seemingly successful, it turned out that the one of the most powerful entities, the Leviathans, from Purgatory held on to Castiel, and overpowered and took control of him.[8] When the Leviathans leave to take over new forms, Castiel was presumed dead, but survived – apparently resurrected by God yet again. Dean later accidentally finds Castiel as an amnesiac healer called Emmanuel.[9] After taking on Sam\'s madness and experience in Hell in order to save the Winchesters and redeem himself for what he did to Sam, Castiel had become insane and fell into a coma. However, he awakens and his sanity is returned to an extent when a signal was sent to all angels upon the discovery of the Word of God and the appointment of a new prophet.[10] He then aids the Winchester brothers against Dick Roman, only to be transported to Purgatory with Dean.[11]\n</string>
    <string name="castiel_desc3">While Dean returns, Castiel has not returned with him. While his condition is initially unknown, it\'s revealed that he spent most of his time running from Leviathans and that he didn\'t escape Purgatory with Dean as he had planned to stay as a form of penance. However, he was eventually released from the monster realm by an incursion of angels under the orders of a mysterious but powerful angel named Naomi and would rejoin the Winchester brothers and tried to become a hunter himself. But after a long while, Castiel learned that Naomi has been controlling him ever since she got him out of Purgatory and compelling him to find the angel tablet, at any cost, even going as far as killing Dean. When he almost did so, after that, Castiel then teamed up with Metatron when the angel convinced him to help him close the gates of Heaven. So after collecting the heart of a nephilim and the bow of cupid, Metatron is eventually captured by Naomi but escapes and kills her, only for Cas to discover Metatron\'s betrayal and plan to cause all angels in Heaven, even the imprisoned ones, to fall to Earth.\n</string>
    <string name="castiel_desc4">After being stripped of his grace by Metatron in order to expel all angels from Heaven, Castiel spends the next three months on Earth as a human. After being captured and tortured by an angel named Malachi, Castiel steals the grace of Theo and returns to his original status as an angel (previously being promoted to a Seraph). Castiel later assists Dean with expelling the angel Gadreel from Sam and heals Sam\'s wounds. After Dean leaves with Crowley to find a way to defeat Abaddon, Castiel also leaves to begin a search for Metatron and Gadreel while being pursued by other angels and eventually kills rebel leader Bartholomew and assumes command of his faction but a deception of Metatron\'s makes him lose his army but instead teamed up with angels Gadreel and Hannah to infiltrate Heaven and destroy the angel tablet, cutting off Metatron\'s power to allow Dean to kill him. Though successful, Dean and Gadreel were killed, while Castiel locked up Metatron. He has currently left Heaven as he doesn\'t want to be a leader and was dying due to his burning-out grace before Crowley saved him with Adina\'s grace. He has since reclaimed the last of his own grace and restored to full power and being a Seraph once again.\n</string>
    <string name="castiel_desc5">Castiel\'s legacy has seemed to have become legendary among angels and demons alike, as many recognize him as the only angel who defied God\'s rules and cooperated with humans on his own decision, which he is either loathed or respected for. He is also the only angel to have been killed, and been resurrected multiple times. He is the only known angel who has repeatedly been resurrected by God so he could help Sam and Dean Winchester.</string>
    <string name="bobby_desc">Bobby Singer was a hunter, close friend and father figure to Sam and Dean Winchester. Bobby grew up with an abusive father, who Bobby shot and killed when he was a teenager while protecting his mother. Bobby buried his father in the salvage yard.A mechanic by trade, Bobby became a hunter after he had to kill his wife Karen Singer when she was possessed by a demon. Rufus Turner is the hunter who exorcised the demon and helped cover up Karen\'s death. It was Rufus who introduced Bobby to the world of the supernatural, and they hunted together for many years until a hunt went wrong in Omaha around 1993. They become estranged after this although they had contact and some reconciliation from 2008 until Rufus\' death in 2011.Bobby\'s guilt over Karen\'s death causes her to inhabit his dreams. She is later resurrected by Death and turns into a zombie and he has to kill her again,which causes him more grief.Bobby has known the Winchesters since at least 1991 - he gave an 8-year-old Sam an amulet as a Christmas present for his father, which he eventually gave to Dean. Bobby also played catch with Dean, and took the brothers deer hunting.John Winchester and Bobby were not necessarily on good terms - Dean comments that the last time Bobby saw John he nearly \"filled him with buckshot.\" It is to Bobby\'s place that Sam and Dean go to grieve after John\'s death. After this Bobby\'s relationship with the Winchesters grows even closer, and he becomes both father figure and friend.\n</string>
    <string name="bobby_desc1">When Sam and Dean try to go after Lilith without him, Bobby tells them \"Family don\'t end with blood, boy.\" and more than once Dean tells Bobby he\'s like a father to him. Bobby has listed Dean as his official next of kin. In 2009, Bobby is paralyzed from the waist down after stabbing himself with Ruby\'s knife to overcome his own demonic possession when Meg orders him to kill Dean.\n</string>
    <string name="bobby_desc2">Bobby sells his soul to Crowley in exchange for information on Death\'s location. Crowley also makes it possible for Bobby to walk again. He says that he will return Bobby\'s soul after Lucifer is defeated. It is later revealed that Bobby was given the standard ten years to live until his soul is dragged to Hell. Bobby is able to trick Crowley and negotiate the return of his soul.Sam visits Bobby on his release from Lucifer\'s Cage, and Bobby agrees to keep Sam\'s return a secret from Dean, who Bobby sees at having a chance at a normal life. Following his reunion with Sam, Dean (worried because of Sam\'s cold and relentless behavior) calls on Bobby for support. A soulless Sam later turns their closeness against Bobby when Balthazar tells Sam that the spell to keep his soul from being returned requires the blood of his father but that needn\'t come from the \"father of your blood,\" and he tries to kill Bobby. Following the return of Sam\'s soul, Bobby finds it initially difficult to be around Sam because of this assault.Bobby continued to work with Sam and Dean hunting the Mother of Monsters - Eve. While possessed by a creature she created, he kills his old friend Rufus Turner.Bobby is the first one to voice concerns about Castiel\'s activities, and is with Sam and Dean when Castiel appears. He helps to send the souls back to Purgatory, and tries to keep Sam and Dean grounded in the aftermath of losing Castiel, Sam\'s hallucinations, and the appearance of the leviathans.\n</string>
    <string name="bobby_desc3">After being shot by Dick Roman, the leader of the Leviathans, Bobby lapses into a coma and dies. His last word is an affectionate \"Idjits\" to Sam and Dean. However, Bobby refuses to go with his reaper, remaining on Earth as a spirit to help the Winchesters, when he is able. However, after becoming a vengeful spirit temporarily, he asked Sam and Dean to put him to rest, which they did. His last request was for them not to give into vengeance like he did and when their time came, to move on.Unfortunately, instead of going to Heaven where he belonged once his flask was burned, on Crowley\'s orders, rogue reaper Ajay takes Bobby to Hell instead where he is tortured by demons in the visage of Sam and Dean taunting him. Eventually, the real Sam rescues him and releases Bobby\'s soul unto Heaven where it belongs with help from the angel Naomi.After arriving in Heaven, Bobby enjoys his new life in his Heaven which is a replica of his old house until Sam and Castiel contact him for help with breaking Metatron out of prison in hopes of removing the Mark of Cain from Dean. Bobby, though he feels himself rusty, helps and is punished in an unknown manner for it, though he leaves Sam a note in which he states that it was worth it.</string>
    <string name="crowley_desc">Fergus Roderick MacLeod (c. 1661 - 1723) was a human, who after death became Crowley; a powerful demon who was the former King of the Crossroads and the King of Hell following Lucifer\'s possible demise. Although he initially served with Lilith as her right-hand man, he went rogue in Season 5 after her death and Lucifer\'s release, aiding the Winchester brothers in resealing the latter back into his cage. With the power vacuum in Hell unoccupied, he appointed himself the new King of Hell.\n</string>
    <string name="crowley_desc1">Crowley allied with Sam and Dean in Season 5 against Lucifer to obtain the Four Horsemen\'s rings with them to protect himself, then with Castiel to obtain the power of Purgatory and briefly with Raphael after his betrayal in Season 6, and then with the Winchesters again in Season 7 against the ambitious Leviathans. However, in Season 8, he cuts his allegiance to the Winchesters and Castiel, seeking vengeance as well as attempting to capture the Prophet Kevin Tran and The Word of God to further his own goals, only to be captured by the Winchesters as part of their plan to close the gates of Hell. In Season 9, Crowley was temporarily Sam and Dean\'s captive while being hunted by Abaddon as part of her plan to take over Hell. However, upon being freed as part of a deal with Dean, he has rightfully resumed his post. After Dean was killed by Metatron and revived by the First Blade, Crowley guided Dean through the process of becoming a demon. The two spent a significant amount of time together until Dean was cured.\n</string>
    <string name="crowley_desc2">Crowley was overthrown and held as a slave when Lucifer escaped from his cage. Crowley was forced to do slave work until he managed to flee.\n</string>
    <string name="crowley_desc3">Crowley\'s role is often shifting from main antagonist to anti-hero. He was an anti-hero in Season 5, one of the two main antagonists in Season 6, an anti-hero in Season 7, the main antagonist of Season 8, and an anti-hero of Season 9 and Season 10 once more. However, in all of his duration\'s as an anti-hero, he is still openly an antagonist usually pulling a life-threatening stunt on the Winchesters after assisting them. He is currently the longest lasting antagonist in the series.</string>
    <string name="lucifer_desc">Lucifer, also known as The Devil, Light Bringer, The Morning Star, and Satan, is the second of the four Archangels created by God and is his favorite son. He is also a fallen archangel, and the first fallen angel. He is a recurring character, was the main antagonist of Season 5, and the secondary antagonist of Season 7 and Season 11. He is the original ruler of Hell and the creator of demons, seen by them as a father figure and their god.[2][3] As the second-born Archangel, he is the younger brother of Michael, and older brother of Raphael and Gabriel.\n</string>
    <string name="lucifer_desc1">According to Gabriel, Lucifer is, or at least was, God\'s favorite and most beloved celestial, but when God asked for all angels to bow down to humanity, Lucifer refused both out of jealousy and wounded pride over being commanded to bow to what he saw as a broken, flawed, and murderous species and no longer feeling he was God\'s favorite creation.[4] This was caused by the Mark of Cain corrupting him and boosting his dislike towards humanity.[5] He waged a war against God but was eventually cast out of Heaven by God, and banished to Hell by Michael. All of Azazel\'s actions were motivated with the goal of eventually releasing Lucifer from his cage in Hell.[3]\n</string>
    <string name="lucifer_desc2">Like all other angels, Lucifer must have the permission of a strong enough human to use as his vessel, as he can not forcefully possess a person. Being an archangel, Lucifer possesses much more power than any normal angel, every pagan, and also every demon and species of monsters, most of whom deify him, thus being among the most powerful entities the Winchesters have ever encountered.[6] But his power causes regular vessels to decay and required to drink vast amounts of demon blood or possess either his true vessel (Sam Winchester) or an alternate more stable vessel (Castiel).\n</string>
    <string name="lucifer_desc3">Eventually, he was finally freed and allowed to roam the Earth when the final seal (the death of Lilith) was broken by Sam.[3] Freed from his cage, he took action to bring about the Apocalypse and cleanse the Earth (aka \"The last perfect handiwork of God\") of human beings (the flawed creation). Even after Lucifer was able to possess Sam Winchester, his true vessel, Sam\'s love for his brother Dean allowed Sam to regain control of his body, and seal himself, Lucifer, Michael, and Adam Milligan back in Lucifer\'s Cage.[7]\n</string>
    <string name="lucifer_desc4">After the release of the Darkness about five years later, the cage was damaged and Lucifer (whilst he still couldn\'t leave it) began reaching out to Sam to get him to return to Hell and release Lucifer so he could return to the world, working with Rowena to achieve this. Though Sam refused, Castiel said \"yes\" and Lucifer returned to the world in Castiel\'s body.\n</string>
    <string name="lucifer_desc5">After reconciling with God, Lucifer joined him, Sam, and Dean in an attack to defeat Amara. However, Amara, not wanting to be re-imprisoned, overpowered God and in her rage, she pulled Lucifer from Castiel\'s body when he went to attack her and help his father. It is unknown where he was banished to, but he survived and was able to take possession of Vince Vincente, an aging musician.</string>
    <string name="rowena_desc">Rowena MacLeod is an extremely powerful witch, and the mother of Crowley, who was originally named Fergus Roderick MacLeod. She is also the grandmother of Gavin MacLeod, and is of Scottish descent. She was one of the main antagonists of Season 10. In Season 11 she continued her efforts to gain power, eventually teaming up with Lucifer upon promises of being his queen. After helping Lucifer free himself, Lucifer snapped her neck so he couldn\'t be trapped in the Cage by her again. However, she was able to resurrect herself with a spell she had prepared before</string>
    <string name="john_desc">John Eric Winchester (1954-2006) was the son of Henry and Millie Winchester[1], the husband of Mary Winchester, and the father of Dean and Sam Winchester[2] and Adam Milligan.[3] Seeking revenge after his wife was killed by the demon Azazel, John became a hunter and raised his two oldest sons to fight the supernatural. When Dean was 26 and Sam was about to get his law education started, John mysteriously disappeared, which caused his sons to go back into hunting in order to find him.[2] Eventually they found John who sought the demon-killing Colt gun to kill Azazel,[4] but the three were caught in a car crash after a brutal encounter with the demon.[5] Soon after John made a deal with Azazel to bring back Dean from death and went to Hell for it,[6] but eventually escaped when the Devil\'s Gate was opened and assisted Dean as a spirit to finally kill Azazel before moving on.[7]\n</string>
    <string name="john_desc1">Before becoming a hunter, John was a Vietnam War veteran (USMC) from Lawrence, Kansas, he worked as a mechanic and was eventually co-owner (with Mike Guenther) of a garage in Lawrence. John also served as a temporary vessel for the Archangel Michael and a temporary vessel for the demon Azazel in said\'s demon\'s first true onscreen appearance.[8]</string>
    <string name="god_desc">God, initially known to Sam and Dean as Chuck Shurley, is a powerful primordial being who created the universe and nearly everything it contains, including the human soul. The Darkness, his older sister, is the only entity surpassing his power, with the Horseman Death, prior to his demise, having been his equal.[1][2]\n</string>
    <string name="god_desc1">Together, he and The Darkness serve as the balance in the Universe, as the dark cannot exist without the light and vice versa. If either one of them is lost or destroyed, the Universe would begin to collapse on itself and everything in it and existence would cease to exist. His sister couldn\'t resist in destroying whatever he was setting out to create so he created four archangels and, with them by his side, waged war against her and then locked her away with a mark which he entrusted to his most loved and valued angel, Lucifer. However, over time, after God created the Universe, the mark corrupted Lucifer and drew him to rebel when God created humankind. After Lucifer was bound in Hell, God left Heaven and went into seclusion on Earth.\n</string>
    <string name="god_desc2">After thousands of years, God eventually reappeared and partially aided in the Apocalypse. After the Apocalypse was averted, he disappeared again. Five years later, when his sister was released, God was originally willing to let his creations be wiped from existence and let Amara take over. But after being convinced by Metatron and the Winchesters, God eventually decided to help stop Amara. After being fatally injured by his sister, God was then healed by her and they both departed the Earth together.</string>
    <string name="amara_desc">The Darkness, often called by another name, Amara, is a supremely powerful primordial entity who has existed since before the beginning of time, predating both God and Death, who were of similar age.[1] Sometime later after her brother God came into being, he created the Archangels to fight a terrible war against her. Not even the combined power of God and the Archangels could destroy her, so God tricked and sealed her away by using the Mark of Cain as a lock and key.[2][3] God revealed that he chose not to kill her in her weakened state as she needed to exist with himself so reality wouldn\'t be destroyed.[4] Whilst the Archangels battled her and thus knew of her existence, she is so ancient and mysterious that the Demons and even the Angels, except for Metatron, didn\'t believe she existed or was locked away. However, Metatron knew about her and who she was, as he was God\'s scribe. Both Heaven and Hell thought it to be a \"myth\" or \"scary bedtime story\", told to keep others in line.[5]\n</string>
    <string name="amara_desc1">When Rowena used a spell from the Book of the Damned in order to free Dean Winchester of the Mark (which he gained from Cain to kill Abaddon and had been bearing it since), the Darkness was unleashed once again.[2] While on Earth, The Darkness has taken the body of a female baby, Amara. Since regaining her power by consuming human souls, she matured and grew into a young woman in just a few months. As a young woman, she has also developed a romantic affection for Dean, and is possibly in love with him.\n</string>
    <string name="amara_desc2">With Dean\'s help, the Darkness reconciled with her brother and departed the Earth with him, but not before leaving Dean a thank you present.</string>
    <string name="mary_desc">Mary Winchester (née Campbell) (born December 5, 1954) is a retired hunter, the daughter of Samuel and Deanna Campbell, the wife of John Winchester, and the mother of Dean and Sam Winchester. She was killed by the demon Azazel exactly six months after Sam was born, which spurred John into becoming a hunter to kill Azazel in revenge and raising their sons as hunters as well. 33 years later, after Dean reunited God and the Darkness, she was resurrected by the latter as a thank-you gift for Dean,she will have major apperence in season 12</string>

</resources>
